trivia:
  # How long should players have to guess?
  duration: 120

  # The chance to use a challenge instead of a normal game.
  # 0 = never use challenges, 100 = always use challenges
  challenge-chance: 20

  challenges:
    # Chance that a trivia question will be replaced with
    # "Who is at rank [1-5] in ChatGame?"
    player-in-position: 2

    # Chance that a trivia question will be replaced with
    # "Who is at rank [1-5] for [random game] in ChatGame?"
    player-in-game-position: 2

    # Chance that a trivia question will be replaced with "Who won last round?"
    won-last-round: 2

    # Chance that a trivia question will be replaced with
    # "What was the answer to the previous question?"
    answer-last-round: 2

    # Chance that a trivia question will be replaced with "How many players are online right now?"
    players-online: 2

    # Chance that a trivia question will be replaced with "How many points do you currently have?",
    # where the answer is different depending on who answers.
    current-points: 0.5

    # Chance that a trivia question will be replaced with "How many [item]s do
    # you need to craft [item]?"
    # Does not include recipes that only contain one item & item type
    crafting-recipe: 5

    # Chance that a trivia question will be replaced with "Name a crafting recipe that includes [item]."
    crafting-ingredient: 5

  questions:
    # The unique name of the question. It's not used, but must be unique
    Notch:
      # The question to display
      question: 'What is the screen-name of Markus Persson?'
      # A list of answers - Any of these will be accepted, but only the one answered appears.
      answers:
        - 'Notch' # If it only has one answer, just put it here!
      points: 1

    NetherPortalObsidian:
      question: 'What is the minimum amount of obsidian needed for a nether portal?'
      answers: # You can list multiple answers if people might answer differently
        - '10'
        - 'Ten'
      points: 1

    RarestOre:
      question: 'What is the rarest ore in Minecraft?'
      max-version: 1.16.4
      use-regex: true # You can enable regex for the answers to condense answers.
      answers:
        - 'Emerald(s|\sOre)?' # Catches Emerald, Emeralds, and Emerald Ore!
      points: 1

    RarestOre1_17+:
      question: 'What is the rarest ore in Minecraft?'
      min-version: 1.17
      use-regex: true
      answers:
        - 'Deepslate Emerald(\sOre)?'
      points: 1

    Fatigue:
      question: 'Which potion effect is applied exclusively by Elder Guardians?'
      answers:
        - 'Mining Fatigue'
      points: 1

    Dimensions:
      question: 'How many dimensions are there in minecraft?'
      answers:
        - '3'
        - 'Three'
      points: 1

    EndPortalEyes:
      question: 'How many Eyes of Ender are needed to complete an end portal?'
      answers:
        - '12'
        - 'Twelve'
      points: 1

    Sweden:
      question: 'In which country was Minecraft made?'
      answers:
        - 'Sweden'
      points: 1

    Repeater:
      question: 'How many tick options are there on a redstone repeater?'
      answers:
        - '4'
        - 'Four'
      points: 1

    PistonPush:
      question: 'How many blocks can a piston push?'
      answers:
        - '12'
        - 'Twelve'
      points: 1

    EndermenEyes:
      question: 'What colour are an endermen''s eyes?'
      answers:
        - 'Purple'
      points: 1

    CreeperModel:
      question: 'Which entity was being worked on when they accidentally created the creeper model?'
      answers:
        - 'Pig'
        - 'A pig'
      points: 1

    AnvilVariants:
      question: 'How many variants of anvils are there?'
      answers:
        - '3'
        - 'Three'
      points: 1

    Dinnerbone:
      question: 'What name can be given to a mob that will turn it upside-down?'
      answers:
        - 'Dinnerbone'
        - 'Grumm'
      points: 1

    Jeb:
      question: 'What name can be given to a sheep that will make it change colours?'
      answers:
        - 'jeb_'
      points: 1

    WoolColours:
      question: 'How many colours of wool are there?'
      answers:
        - '16'
        - 'Sixteen'
      points: 1

    BannerPatterns:
      question: 'How many banner patterns are there?'
      answers:
        - '6'
        - 'Six'
      points: 1

    FishingRodDurability:
      question: 'What is the maximum durability of a fishing rod?'
      answers:
        - '64'
      points: 1

    FindNetherFortress:
      question: 'What is the name of the advancement you get when you find a Nether Fortress for the first time?'
      answers:
        - 'A Terrible Fortress'
      points: 1

    EndSecondAdvancement:
      question: 'What is the second advancement you get in the End?'
      answers:
        - 'Free the End'
      points: 1

    OlBetsyDescription:
      question: 'What is the description for the advancement "Ol'' Betsy"?'
      # The minimum version this question will appear on.
      # This lets you make questions that are version-specific if needed!
      required-version: 1.14
      answers:
        - 'Shoot a Crossbow'
      points: 1

    FletchingTableCategory:
      question: 'In which tab of the Creative Menu does the Fletching Table appear?'
      min-version: 1.14 # Same thing as required-version
      max-version: 1.19.3
      answers:
        - 'Decoration Blocks'
      points: 1

    FletchingTableCategory1_19_4+:
      question: 'In which tab of the Creative Menu does the Fletching Table appear?'
      min-version: 1.19.4 # Same thing as required-version
      answers:
        - 'Decoration Blocks'
      points: 1

    PhantomMembraneCategory:
      question: 'In which tab of the Creative Menu does Phantom Membrane appear?'
      # The maximum version that a question may appear in.
      # This lets you keep old questions for backwards compatibility, and specify
      # the new version's question without having an inaccurate version
      # You can also use this & min-version to prepare questions for new versions in advance,
      # so they'll automatically switch when the server upgrades!
      max-version: 1.19.3
      answers:
        - 'Brewing'
      points: 1

    PhantomMembraneCategory1_19_4+:
      question: 'In which tab of the Creative Menu does Phantom Membrane appear?'
      min-version: 1.19.4
      answers:
        - 'Ingredients'
      points: 1

    SmallestMenuCategory:
      question: 'Which tab of the Creative Menu has the fewest items?'
      max-version: 1.19.3
      answers:
        - 'Transportation'
      points: 1

    SmallestMenuCategory1_19_4+:
      question: 'Which tab of the Creative Menu has the fewest items?'
      min-version: 1.19.4
      answers:
        - 'Redstone'
        - 'Redstone Blocks'
      points: 1

    MinecartTypes:
      question: 'How many types of minecarts are there?'
      answers:
        - '7'
        - 'Seven'
      points: 1

    CreepersScared:
      question: 'What are creepers scared of?'
      answers:
        - 'Cats'
        - 'Ocelots'
        - 'Cat'
        - 'Ocelot'
      points: 1

    Toast:
      question: 'What can you name a rabbit to give it a special texture?'
      answers:
        - 'Toast'
      points: 1

    ShulkerTypes:
      question: 'How many types of Shulker Box are there?'
      answers:
        - '17'
        - 'Seventeen'
      points: 1

    MusicDisc11:
      question: 'What level of redstone power does a jukebox emit via comparator when playing music disc 11?'
      answers:
        - '11'
      points: 1

    EnchantingLapis:
      question: 'Which type of item is consumed when enchanting?'
      answers:
        - 'Lapis'
        - 'Lapis Lazuli'
      points: 1

    BookPageLimit:
      question: 'In vanilla, how many pages can a written book have?'
      use-regex: true
      answers:
        - '100'
        - '((One|A|1)\s)?Hundred'
      points: 1

    Herobrine:
      question: 'Who is the mythical character with the Steve skin that has white eyes?'
      answers:
        - 'Herobrine'
      points: 1

    MusicDiscName:
      question: 'Name a music disc.'
      answers:
        - '13'
        - 'cat'
        - 'blocks'
        - 'chirp'
        - 'far'
        - 'mall'
        - 'mellohi'
        - 'stal'
        - 'strad'
        - 'ward'
        - '11'
        - 'wait'
        - 'otherside'
        - 'Pigstep'
        - 'Relic'
      points: 1

    ShulkerSlots:
      question: 'How many slots does a shulker box have?'
      answers:
        - '27'
      points: 2

    FastestPlant:
      question: 'Which plant grows the fastest in Minecraft?'
      answers:
        - 'Bamboo'
      points: 2

    BambooOutsideJungles:
      question: 'Outside of jungles, where else can you find bamboo?'
      answers:
        - 'Shipwreck'
        - 'Shipwrecks'
      points: 2

    SpawnInAllDimensions:
      question: 'Which mob spawns naturally in all three dimensions?'
      answers:
        - 'Endermen'
        - 'Enderman'
      points: 2

    JumpHeight:
      question: 'How high does a player jump?'
      use-regex: true
      answers:
        - '1.25\s?blocks?'
        - '1 1/4\s?blocks?'
      points: 2

    Version1_4:
      question: 'What was the 1.4 release of Minecraft: Java Edition called?'
      answers:
        - 'The Pretty Scary Update'
        - 'Pretty Scary Update'
        - 'Pretty Scary'
      points: 2

    Version1_5:
      question: 'What was the 1.5 release of Minecraft: Java Edition called?'
      answers:
        - 'The Redstone Update'
        - 'Redstone Update'
        - 'Redstone'
      points: 2

    Version1_6:
      question: 'What was the 1.6 release of Minecraft: Java Edition called?'
      answers:
        - 'The Horse Update'
        - 'Horse Update'
        - 'Horse'
      points: 2

    Version1_7:
      question: 'What was the 1.7 release of Minecraft: Java Edition called?'
      answers:
        - 'The Update That Changed The World'
        - 'Update That Changed The World'
      points: 2

    Version1_8:
      question: 'What was the 1.8 release of Minecraft: Java Edition called?'
      answers:
        - 'The Bountiful Update'
        - 'Bountiful Update'
        - 'Bountiful'
      points: 2

    Version1_9:
      question: 'What was the 1.9 release of Minecraft: Java Edition called?'
      answers:
        - 'The Combat Update'
        - 'Combat Update'
        - 'Combat'
      points: 2

    Version1_10:
      question: 'What was the 1.10 release of Minecraft: Java Edition called?'
      answers:
        - 'The Frostburn Update'
        - 'Frostburn Update'
        - 'Frostburn'
      points: 2

    Version1_11:
      question: 'What was the 1.11 release of Minecraft: Java Edition called?'
      answers:
        - 'The Exploration Update'
        - 'Exploration Update'
        - 'Exploration'
      points: 2

    Version1_12:
      question: 'What was the 1.12 release of Minecraft: Java Edition called?'
      answers:
        - 'The World of Color Update'
        - 'The World of Colour Update'
        - 'World of Color Update'
        - 'World of Colour Update'
        - 'World of Color'
        - 'World of Colour'
      points: 2

    Version1_13:
      question: 'What was the 1.13 release of Minecraft: Java Edition called?'
      answers:
        - 'The Update Aquatic'
        - 'Update Aquatic'
      points: 2

    Version1_14:
      question: 'What was the 1.14 release of Minecraft: Java Edition called?'
      answers:
        - 'Village and Pillage'
      points: 2

    Version1_15:
      question: 'What was the 1.15 release of Minecraft: Java Edition called?'
      answers:
        - 'Buzzy Bees'
      points: 2

    Version1_16:
      question: 'What was the 1.16 release of Minecraft: Java Edition called?'
      answers:
        - 'Nether Update'
      points: 2

    Version1_17:
      question: 'What was the 1.17 release of Minecraft: Java Edition called?'
      use-regex: true
      answers:
        # Accepts "Caves and Cliffs Part 1", "Caves & Cliffs: Part I", and variations in between!
        - 'Caves (and|&) Cliffs(:? Part (1|I))?'
      points: 2

    Version1_18:
      question: 'What was the 1.18 release of Minecraft: Java Edition called?'
      use-regex: true
      answers:
        # Accepts "Caves and Cliffs Part 2", "Caves & Cliffs: Part II", and variations in between!
        - 'Caves (and|&) Cliffs:? Part (2|II)'
      points: 2

    Version1_19:
      question: 'What was the 1.19 release of Minecraft: Java Edition called?'
      answers:
        - 'The Wild Update'
        - 'Wild Update'
        - 'Wild'
      points: 2

    Version1_20:
      question: 'What was the 1.20 release of Minecraft: Java Edition called?'
      use-regex: true
      answers:
        - 'Trails\s?(and|&)\s?Tales'
      points: 2

    NoReleaseYear:
      question: 'What is the only year since the release of Minecraft that had no major deployment?'
      answers:
        - '2015'
        - '''15'
      points: 2

    Johnny:
      question: 'What name can be given to a Vindicator that will make it attack other mobs?'
      answers:
        - 'Johnny'
      points: 2

    HoglinsFear:
      question: 'What are hoglins afraid of?'
      answers:
        - 'Warped Fungus'
        - 'Nether Portal'
        - 'Portal'
        - 'Respawn Anchor'
      points: 2

    LightningWitch:
      question: 'What will create a witch when it hits a villager?'
      answers:
        - 'Lightning'
      points: 2

    UnobtainablePotion:
      question: 'Name a potion effect that is impossible to get in vanilla survival mode.'
      answers:
        - 'Luck'
        - 'Unluck'
        - 'Health Boost'
      points: 2

    NightVision:
      question: 'Brewing which item will give you a night vision potion?'
      answers:
        - 'Golden Carrot'
      points: 2

    MinecraftDay:
      question: 'How long is a minecraft day in real time?'
      answers:
        - '20 minutes'
        - '20m'
        - '20 m'
        - '20minutes'
        - '20min'
        - '20 min'
      points: 2

    GameTicks:
      question: 'How many game ticks are there in a second?'
      answers:
        - '20'
        - 'Twenty'
      points: 2

    SeecretFriday:
      question: 'How many "Seecret Friday" updates were there during the Alpha stage of development?'
      answers:
        - '7'
        - 'Seven'
      points: 2

    ArrowCrafting:
      question: 'When arrows first became craftable in early development, what was used instead of flint for the tip?'
      answers:
        - 'Iron'
        - 'Iron ingot'
      points: 2

    CakeBites:
      question: 'How many bites does a cake have?'
      answers:
        - '7'
        - 'Seven'
      points: 2

    GhastSounds:
      question: 'Ghast sounds were created by distorting the sounds of which animal?'
      answers:
        - 'A cat'
        - 'Cat'
      points: 2

    BedrockEdition:
      question: 'What is the alternative to Minecraft: Java Edition?'
      answers:
        - 'Minecraft: Bedrock Edition'
        - 'Bedrock Edition'
        - 'Bedrock'
      points: 2

    C418:
      question: 'C418''s skin has what block as a head?'
      answers:
        - 'Jukebox'
        - 'A Jukebox'
      points: 2

    MojangBanner:
      question: 'What item is used to craft a Mojang Banner Pattern?'
      answers:
        - 'Enchanted Golden Apple'
      points: 2

    CaveGame:
      question: 'What was Minecraft originally going to be called?'
      answers:
        - 'Cave Game'
        - 'Cavegame'
      points: 2

    AxolotlMiningFatigue:
      required-version: 1.17
      question: 'Which mob can remove Mining Fatigue from the player?'
      answers:
        - 'Axolotl'
      points: 2

    BabyPandaSneeze:
      required-version: 1.14
      question: 'What is the chance of a baby panda dropping a slime ball when sneezing?'
      use-regex: true
      answers:
        - '0\.1( ?%| percent)?' # 0.1, 0.1%, 0.1 %, 0.1 percent
      points: 2

    TurtleLightning:
      question: 'What does a turtle drop when struck by lightning?'
      answers:
        - 'A Bowl'
        - 'Bowl'
      points: 2

    TintedGlass:
      required-version: 1.17
      question: 'What type of glass can be picked up without silk touch?'
      answers:
        - 'Tinted'
        - 'Tinted Glass'
      points: 2

    ShearsWool:
      question: 'What level of Efficiency is needed on shears to instantly mine wool?'
      answers:
        - '5'
        - 'Five'
        - 'V'
      points: 2

    DevelopmentEndermanEyes:
      question: 'During development, what colour were endermen''s eyes?'
      answers:
        - 'Green'
      points: 2

    ChainmailCrafting:
      question: 'Prior to Java Edition 1.8, what could you use to craft chainmail armour?'
      answers:
        - 'Fire'
      points: 2

    BookshelvesEnchanting:
      question: 'How many bookshelves do you need for a level 30 enchanting table?'
      answers:
        - '15'
        - 'Fifteen'
      points: 2

    EndermanTeleport:
      question: 'How far can an enderman teleport (in a given axis)?'
      answers:
        - '32'
        - '32 blocks'
      points: 2

    GhastHealth:
      question: 'How many hearts does a ghast have?'
      answers:
        - '5'
        - '5 hearts'
      points: 2

    OldestMob:
      question: 'Other than the player, what''s the oldest mob in Minecraft (that''s still in the game)?'
      use-regex: true
      answers:
        - '(A\s)?Creeper\s?'
      points: 2

    SnifferGrow:
      question: 'Placing a sniffer egg on which block will make it hatch faster?'
      min-version: 1.20
      answers:
        - 'Moss'
        - 'Moss Block'
        - 'A Moss Block'
      points: 2

    BabyHeadSize:
      question: 'Which baby mob does not have a large head in comparison to its body?'
      answers:
        - 'Villager'
        - 'Villagers'
      points: 2

    EndStoneTexture:
      question: 'End Stone is an altered version of which block''s texture?'
      answers:
        - 'Cobble'
        - 'Cobblestone'
      points: 2

    HalloweenBats:
      question: 'Which mob spawns more frequently between 20 October and 3 November?'
      answers:
        - 'Bat'
        - 'Bats'
      points: 2

    UnusedMob:
      question: 'Name a mob that can only be spawned through commands.'
      answers:
        - 'Giant'
        - 'Illusioner'
        # Not zombie horses - they can be spawned through spawn eggs
      points: 2

    Minceraft:
      question: 'What has a 1 in 10,000 chance of replacing "Minecraft" on the title screen?'
      answers:
        - 'Minceraft'
      points: 2

    LodestoneFire:
      question: 'Which item can be crafted with a netherite ingot that is NOT immune to lava/fire?'
      answers:
        - 'Lodestone'
      points: 2

    PotterySherdName:
      question: 'Name a Pottery Sherd.'
      min-version: 1.20
      answers:
        - 'Angler'
        - 'Archer'
        - 'Arms Up'
        - 'Blade'
        - 'Brewer'
        - 'Burn'
        - 'Danger'
        - 'Explorer'
        - 'Friend'
        - 'Heart'
        - 'Heartbreak'
        - 'Howl'
        - 'Miner'
        - 'Mourner'
        - 'Plenty'
        - 'Prize'
        - 'Sheaf'
        - 'Shelter'
        - 'Skull'
        - 'Snort'
      points: 2

    PotterySherdWardenDepiction:
      question: 'Which pottery sherd depicts an early design for the Warden?'
      min-version: 1.20
      answers:
        - 'Mourner'
      points: 2

    MobVote:
      question: 'Name a mob that was added to Minecraft as a result of a Mob Vote.'
      answers:
        - 'Phantom'
        - 'Panda'
        - 'Glow Squid'
        - 'Allay'
        - 'Sniffer'
      points: 2

    MobVoteLoss:
      question: 'Name a mob that lost its Mob Vote, and was NOT added to the game.'
      use-regex: true
      answers:
        # 2017
        - '(The )?Barnacle' # Mob A
        - '(The )?Monster of the Ocean Depths' # Mob A alias
        - '(The )?Great Hunger' # Mob B
        - '(The )?Wildfire' # Mob D
        - '(The )?Hovering Inferno' # Mob D alias

        # China Edition release 2018
        - 'Crocodile'
        - 'Golden Monkey'
        - 'Deer'
        - 'Pink Dolphin' # Also called Baiji sometimes - worth including that too?

        # 2020
        - 'Moobloom'
        - 'Iceologer'

        # 2021
        - 'Glare'
        - 'Copper Golem'

        # 2022
        - 'Rascal'
        - 'Tuff Golem'
      points: 3

    WorstFuel:
      max-version: 1.13.2
      question: 'What is the worst fuel to use in a furnace?'
      answers:
        - 'Carpet'
      points: 3

    WorstFuel1_14:
      min-version: 1.14
      question: 'What is the worst fuel to use in a furnace?'
      answers:
        - 'Scaffolding'
        - 'Bamboo'
      points: 3

    GolemIngots:
      question: 'How many iron ingots are required to build an iron golem?'
      answers:
        - '36'
      points: 3

    NoteBlockStartingNote:
      question: 'When a note block is placed, which note does it start on?'
      use-regex: true
      answers:
        - 'F\s?(♯|#|sharp)\s?3?'
      points: 3

    CoalBlockFuelTime:
      question: 'How long can a stack of coal blocks keep a furnace lit for?'
      use-regex: true
      answers:
        - '42\s?days?'
        - '51200\s?seconds?'
        - '853(\.3*)?\s?minutes?'
        - '14(\.2*)?\s?hours?'
      points: 3

    Postmortal:
      question: 'Using a totem of undying will get you which advancement?'
      answers:
        - 'Postmortal'
      points: 3

    Armorer:
      question: 'Which type of villager will sell you a shield?'
      min-version: 1.14
      answers:
        - 'Armorer'
        - 'Armourer'
      points: 3

    Butcher:
      question: 'Which type of villager will sell you rabbit stew?'
      min-version: 1.14
      answers:
        - 'Butcher'
      points: 3

    Cartographer:
      question: 'Which type of villager will sell you an item frame?'
      min-version: 1.14
      answers:
        - 'Cartographer'
      points: 3

    Cleric:
      question: 'Which type of villager will sell you an ender pearl?'
      min-version: 1.14
      answers:
        - 'Cleric'
      points: 3

    Farmer:
      question: 'Which type of villager will sell you a cake?'
      min-version: 1.14
      answers:
        - 'Farmer'
      points: 3

    Fisherman:
      question: 'Which type of villager will sell you a campfire?'
      min-version: 1.14
      answers:
        - 'Fisherman'
        - 'Fisher'
      points: 3

    Fletcher:
      question: 'Which type of villager will sell you a crossbow?'
      min-version: 1.14
      answers:
        - 'Fletcher'
      points: 3

    Leatherworker:
      question: 'Which type of villager will sell you a saddle?'
      min-version: 1.14
      answers:
        - 'Leatherworker'
        - 'Leather Worker'
      points: 3

    Librarian:
      question: 'Which type of villager will sell you a lantern?'
      min-version: 1.14
      answers:
        - 'Librarian'
      points: 3

    Mason:
      question: 'Which type of villager will sell you a block of quartz?'
      min-version: 1.14
      answers:
        - 'Mason'
      points: 3

    Shepherd:
      question: 'Which type of villager will sell you a painting?'
      min-version: 1.14
      answers:
        - 'Shepherd'
      points: 3

    Toolsmith:
      question: 'Which type of villager will sell you an iron pickaxe?'
      min-version: 1.14
      answers:
        - 'Toolsmith'
        - 'Tool Smith'
      points: 3

    Weaponsmith:
      question: 'Which type of villager will sell you an iron sword?'
      min-version: 1.14
      answers:
        - 'Weaponsmith'
        - 'Weapon Smith'
      points: 3

    Alphabet:
      question: 'Type the alphabet backwards.'
      answers:
        - 'ZYXWVUTSRQPONMLKJIHGFEDCBA'
        - 'Z Y X W V U T S R Q P O N M L K J I H G F E D C B A'
      points: 3

    ShulkerItemCount:
      question: 'With shulker boxes, how many items can a player carry?'
      use-regex: true
      answers:
        - '63(,|.)?936( items)?' # Not including armour or shulker boxes
        - '63(,|.)?940( items)?' # Including armour but not shulker boxes
        - '63(,|.)?973( items)?' # Including shulker boxes but not armour
        - '63(,|.)?977( items)?' # Including both
      points: 3

    BlazePowderBrewing:
      question: 'How many potions can be brewed with a single blaze powder as fuel?'
      answers:
        - '20'
        - '20 potions'
      points: 3

    MostUsedIngredient:
      question: 'Which item is used in the most crafting recipes?'
      use-regex: true
      answers:
        - '(A\s)?Stick\s?'
      points: 3

    HoglinBreeding:
      question: 'What is the only naturally spawning hostile mob that can be bred?'
      answers:
        - 'Hoglin'
        - 'Hoglins'
      points: 3

    Grimstone:
      question: 'What was Deepslate originally called (during development)?'
      min-version: 1.17
      answers:
        - 'Grimstone'
      points: 3

    EvokerWololo:
      question: 'Aside from the player, which mob can change the colour of sheep?'
      answers:
        - 'Evoker'
        - 'Evokers'
        - 'An Evoker'
      points: 3

    MostBlocksAndItems:
      question: 'Aside from 1.0, which version of Minecraft added the most blocks/items?'
      use-regex: true
      answers:
        - 'Caves (and|&) Cliffs(:? Part (1|I))?'
        - '1\.17'
      points: 3

    MostMobs:
      question: 'Aside from 1.0, which version of Minecraft added the most mobs?'
      answers:
        - 'The Update Aquatic'
        - 'Update Aquatic'
        - '1.13'
      points: 3

    FewestItemsAdded:
      question: 'Which version of Minecraft added the fewest items/blocks?'
      use-regex: true
      answers:
        - 'Caves (and|&) Cliffs(:? Part (2|II))?'
        - '1\.18'
      points: 3

    SuperflatPreset:
      question: 'Other than "Classic Flat" and "Desert", name a superflat level generation preset.'
      answers:
        - 'Tunnelers'' Dream'
        - 'Water World'
        - 'Overworld'
        - 'Snowy Kingdom'
        - 'Bottomless Pit'
        - 'Redstone Ready'
        - 'The Void'
      points: 3

    SongwriterPigstep:
      question: 'Who wrote the song "Pigstep" for Minecraft?'
      min-version: 1.16
      answers:
        - 'Lena Reine'
      points: 3

    SongwriterOtherside:
      question: 'Who wrote the song "otherside" for Minecraft?'
      min-version: 1.18
      answers:
        - 'Lena Reine'
      points: 3

    SongwriterOtherside:
      question: 'Who wrote the song "5" for Minecraft?'
      min-version: 1.19
      answers:
        - 'Samuel Åberg'
        - 'Samuel Aberg'
      points: 3

    SongwriterRelic:
      question: 'Who wrote the song "Relic" for Minecraft?'
      min-version: 1.20
      answers:
        - 'Aaron Cherof'
      points: 3